[
    { "question": "Which of the following is the Blackforge ancestral hammer?", "answer": "Crisis" },
    { "question": "Who taught Job the ways of the storm?", "answer": "Ester" },
    { "question": "Who was one of the 4 original founders of the School of Wizardry?", "answer": "Harrow" },
    { "question": "Who murdered Dash's parents?", "answer": "Lilith" },
    { "question": "Who single-handedly destroyed and wiped out the Elven and Orc villages?", "answer": "Saul" },
    { "question": "Who was the first person to unite all 4 dark clans?", "answer": "Nero" },
    { "question": "What was Garp known as in his village?", "answer": "The Hero of the Village" },
    { "question": "Why was Elaine separated from the Seven?", "answer": "It was Dark Merlin's doing" },
    { "question": "Why did Merlin kill Saul?", "answer": "It was all a ruse to join the Dark Side" },
    { "question": "Who was Cherry's childhood friend, whom she met after she was sent away from her village?", "answer": "Dash" },
    { "question": "Who's claim to the throne does Elden support?", "answer": "Prince Dewitt Verglas" },
    { "question": "Who in the School of Wizardry has the potential to surpass even Merlin?", "answer": "Esther" },
    { "question": "Who forged Durendal?", "answer": "Zare" },
    { "question": "Who was Hank's brother?", "answer": "Walt" },
    { "question": "Who taught Roland the Flying Heavenly Sword style?", "answer": "A passing wanderer" },
    { "question": "What did Merlin have to do to become Dark Merlin?", "answer": "Give life to Cain and Abel" },
    { "question": "What is Tristan Bittersteel's motivation?", "answer": "To put an end to the injustice and suffering in this world" },
    { "question": "What is Lilith's vow?", "answer": "To annihilate the Humans" },
    { "question": "How did Luna Verglas turn the tides during the Devilkin War?", "answer": "She grabbed a hold of Lilith Devilkiin" },
    { "question": "Why was King Arthur missing for the majority of the Great War?", "answer": "He was in the Void Continent" },
    { "question": "Which of the following is the Verglas family heirloom?", "answer": "Fairfrozen" },
    { "question": "What was Ophelia's role in the Dawn Order?", "answer": "Head Recruiter" },
    { "question": "What happened to Clarissa's top student?", "answer": "He was killed in action" },
    { "question": "Who did NOT run from their village?", "answer": "Cherry" },
    { "question": "Why was Cherry sent away from her village?", "answer": "Her village contracted a plague" },
    { "question": "Who turned Cherry's village into ash and rubble?", "answer": "Maximus" },
    { "question": "Where is Pike currently stationed at?", "answer": "Verhold" },
    { "question": "Who did Lilibeth grow up with?", "answer": "Dash" },
    { "question": "Why was Chandler and Cusack separated?", "answer": "They encountered Lilith" },
    { "question": "Who was Roland's old friend, who grew up in the fighting pits with him?", "answer": "Saul" },
    { "question": "Why is Mikhail a highly revered figure in the Dawn Order?", "answer": "He is one of the very few survivors of the Devilkin War" },
    { "question": "What was Percival's promise?", "answer": "To kill Voidmaw" },
    { "question": "What are the odds someone can wield Excalibur?", "answer": "Zero" },
    { "question": "Who caused the Mana Incursion in the land now known as the Wasteland?", "answer": "Orsted" },
    { "question": "What did Fred find in the ancient vault?", "answer": "Armor" },
    { "question": "What did the Slayer live as, after King Uther's reign?", "answer": "Paul Monroe" },
    { "question": "Why did Gwen leave the School of Wizardry?", "answer": "She found the Book of Prophecies" }
  ]
  